《吸血鬼日记》前情提要
Previously on "The Vampire Diaries"...
达蒙死了
Damon's gone.
我想你催眠我 让我忘记我曾经爱过他
I want you to compel me to forget that I ever loved him.
谁是达蒙·塞尔瓦托
Who is Damon Salvatore?
他就是个禽兽
He was a monster.
这是我女朋友艾薇
That's my girlfriend Ivy.
昨天晚上有人
Somebody killed her last night
就当着我面杀了她
right in front of me.
杀了恩佐也不能让她起死回生
Killing Enzo won't bring her back.
如果我杀了他 我就能安心离开
If I kill him, I can leave this place,
然后再重新开始
and I can start over again.
我想用我的方式杀死他们
I have my own way I like them to die.
吸血鬼都进不了神秘瀑布镇
Vampires can't get into Mystic Falls.
可他们能在附近埋伏着
They can lurk around the borders.
你袭击并催眠的那个女孩 莎拉
Sarah-- the girl you attacked and you compelled...
不
No!
她知道我是什么生物了
Knows what I am.
我妈妈住在神秘瀑布镇很多年了
My mom lived in Mystic Falls for years
生我之前就住那儿了
before she had me.
我们到底在哪儿
Where the hell are we?
1994年
1994.
该死 我们永远都出不去了
My own hell. We're never getting out.
还有其他人在
There's someone else here.
火焰
Incendia.
我们现在是一条绳上的蚂蚱了
We're on the same team.
你是不是一直都是猪队友
Do you always try and kill your teammates?
重要的是你重新拥有了魔力
The important thing is that you have your magic back
因为你的魔力
because your magic is the key
是我们逃出去的关键
to getting the hell out of here.
是啊 我是闯进了总统办公室
And of course, I broke into the oval office
拍了张在窗边眺望肯尼迪机场的照片
and took a picture of myself at the window looking all J.F.K.,
然后我想 天啊 等下
but then I was like, "Wait. How am I gonna get
我要怎么才能把照片发送出去
these photos developed?"
天啊 只回答那个该死的问题就好
Oh, my god! Just answer the damn question.
我们要怎么离开这个隔世之地
How are we gonna get out of this twilight zone?
我有个问题要问
I got a question for you first.
为什么你觉得我们就被困在
Why do you think we're stuck on a repeating loop
1994年5月10号这一天呢
of May 10, 1994,
我们就注定永远要这样
doomed to relive a solar eclipse
重复着日食这一天
forever and ever and ever?
我特么怎么会知道
How the hell should I know?
我听到你对邦妮说
Well, I heard you tell
这是你个人的地狱
Bonnie this place was your own personal hell.
我很好奇是为什么
I'm kind of curious why.
我找到了你要的所有东西了
I found everything you asked for--
开瓶器 地漏 砂轮 果酱
can opener, shower drain, grinding wheel, jam,
小刀 百科全书的O列表
pocket knife, volume "O" Of the encyclopedia,
一片指甲和一只黑色马克笔
a nail, and a black marker.
现在呢
Now what?
手都绑上了怎么告诉你
Can't show you with my hands taped.
邦妮
Bonnie.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 你现在能说了吧
Ok. Fine. How's this pile of crap
这堆破烂东西有什么用
gonna get us out of here?
告诉我你在1994年5月10号做了什么
I'll explain as soon as you tell me
我立刻就告诉你们
what you did on May 10, 1994?
这有什么差别
What difference does it make?
这么说吧 邦妮的魔法
Put it this way. Bonnie's magic is one part
是解决问题的一部分
of the equation.
而我悬而未决的问题是另一部分
My as yet undisclosed knowledge is the other,
也就是说你不用做什么就能回去
which means you would be hitching a ride home for free.
我只是想知道你值不值得我费工夫
I just want to know if you deserve to come along.
或者我可以折磨你
Or I could just torture you until
直到你说出你的方法为止
you say something useful.
如果你折磨我 我会发疯的
If you torture me, I'll get mad,
那样的话我就不会想帮你了
and then I won't want to help you.
他是有多弱智
What kind of person needs to have that
还需要解释的这么直白
explained to them?
态度好点
Play nice.
别想着能和他发展
Stop trying to impress the new guy.
你干嘛不直接告诉他
Why don't you just tell him your story?
也许是因为
Maybe because I don't want to talk
我不想说我做过的最恶劣的事 邦妮
about the worst thing I ever did, Bonnie.
得了 我现在在听
Ooh. Now I'm listening.
吸血鬼
第六季  第四集
日记
翻译：慕斯 windy 冬可可 猫猫 Bunny 络睿
神秘瀑布镇 1994年
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
准备好听恐怖故事了么
Ready for some bad news?
说吧
Unh. Heh.
校对：Bunny
我们快50年没见了 斯特凡
I barely seen you in 50 years, Stefan.
你可以邀请你的哥哥进去
You could invite a brother in.
给我个理由
Give me one good reason why.
去听下你的电话留言
Check your answering machine.
时轴：络睿  压制：呵呵姐   总监：Jophy Bunny
我在试着和你重启友谊新篇章
I'm trying to turn over a new leaf.
我听到你的留言了
Oh, I heard your message.
我还听说你给莱西送花了
I also heard you sent Lexi some flowers
在你让她房顶上被烧死的17年后
17 years after you left her to burn to death on a rooftop.
这个嘛
Well...
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
确实有点迟 不过呢
That's a little late, but I see you're
我看到了你的诚意
trying to make amends.
我只想知道原因
I just want to know why.
这个我可以告诉你 斯特凡
Ugh. Well, I can tell you this, Stefan.
我厌倦了在纽约撕逼
I'm tired of tearing up New York City.
也许是因为趴体 也许是我良心发现了
Maybe it's the partying, maybe it's my conscience.
那也得有个良心才行
I believe that would require one.
然后我突然有那么一瞬的清醒
And then I had this moment of clarity,
想着说 如果
and I said, "Wouldn't it be great
我能每天在自己的床上醒来
"If I just woke up in my own bed
有个全新开始 不是更好吗
and could have a fresh start?"
你一定是达蒙
You must be Damon.
达蒙 这是 额 扎克·塞尔瓦托
Damon, this is, uh, Zach Salvatore.
他是这个房子的主人 他了解家族史
He owns the house now. He knows the family history,
我告诉他 如果你做了越界的行为
and I told him if you got out of line
我会亲自收拾你的
I'd take care of you myself.
你为什么总把我想的那么坏呢
Why are you always expecting the worst
斯特凡
out of me, Stefan?
不是啊 我要是真把你想得那么坏
Oh, I don't. Otherwise, I wouldn't
我就不会让他这么做了
allow this.
进来吧 达蒙
Come on in, Damon.
多谢
Thanks.
准备好重新来过了
You ready to start over?
当然啊
Hell, yeah.
现在
逃跑的姑娘有消息了吗
Hey. Any sign of our runaway girl?
还没 我和卡罗琳都已经
Nope. Caroline and I combed the border
在边界搜寻了3次了
of Mystic Falls 3 times already.
还是没找到萨拉
No sign of Sarah.
公路上也找不到她
She's not any of the roads,
她可能还待在镇上
which means she's probably in Mystic Falls.
这就太糟了 斯特凡
This is bad, Stefan.
一旦她跨越边界
Her compulsion went away as soon as she
对她的催眠就失效了
crossed the border.
她知道我和卡罗琳是吸血鬼
She knows that Caroline and I are vampires.
听着 我得挂了
Listen. I got to go.
我 额 晚点再聊
I'll, uh, talk to you later.
你要去哪儿啊
Where do you think you're going?
额 我要回家
Um, I'm going home.
萨凡纳不是你的家 斯特凡
Savannah's not your home, Stefan.
它只是你逃避 藏身之处
It's an escape, a hiding place.
这里才是你的家
This is your home.
欢迎来到
神秘瀑布镇
不 这曾经是我的家
No. This was my home, but I can no longer
但我已经进不了边界了
enter its borders.
因此 我有个新家了
Therefore, I have a new home.
所以你就心灰意冷
So you're just gonna throw in the towel
回去过你虚假的新生活吗
and go back to your fake new life?
我虚假的新生活
Look. My fake new life ended
在恩佐杀了我真实的女朋友艾薇后 就结束了
when Enzo decided to kill my not-so-fake girlfriend Ivy,
所以我要回家 收拾好行李
so I am going to go home, pack up,
再重新开始
and start over again.
然后假装这儿的一切都不存在
By pretending like your life here never existed.
你会发现 忘记过去
You'd be surprised how easy it is
有多容易 埃琳娜
to forget the past, Elena.
我才不信你
I'm not buying it.
你失去了你哥哥
You lost your brother.
你不可能假装没事
There's no way that you're fine.
你不用担心我
You do not have to worry about me.
我以前又不是没这么做过
It's not like I haven't done this before.
我有自己的一套方法
I have a system.
那就给我看看
Show me. Prove to me
证明它有用
that your system works.
如果我相信你是真的开心
If I believe that you actually are happy,
我就放你走
then I'll let you go,
但如果我不认同 虽然我很有可能不会认同
but if I don't buy it, which I probably won't,
我会一直骚扰你 直到你回家
I will keep harassing you until you come home,
我说的可是 类似 恩佐 那程度的烦恼
and I'm talking about, like, Enzo-sized harassment.
同意吗
Deal?
当然
Sure.
那个逃跑的女孩 莎拉 怎么办
And what about our runaway girl Sarah?
既然我们进不了神秘瀑布镇
Well, we can't step foot in Mystic Falls,
那这事现在就归马特和杰里米管了
so now it's up to Matt and Jeremy.
好样的 全都吐出来吧
Attaboy. Get her all out.
他真的还在吐吗
Is he seriously still wasted?
是的 小废物凌晨4点醉倒
Yeah. Little punk showed up on my doorstep
在我家门口
last night at 4:00 in the morning drunk.
我以为你们两个一起在找莎拉
I thought you two were looking for Sarah together.
我找了 但她显然
I did my part. She is definitely
没有藏在塞尔瓦多的酒柜里
not hiding in the Salvatore liquor cabinet.
你那个厌恶吸血鬼的
Listen. What about your vampire-hating
社区监督队员呢
neighborhood watch guy?
如果莎拉找他求助 那问题就来了
If Sarah goes to him for help, that's a problem.
我现在在去特里普办公室的路上
I'm on my way to Tripp's office now.
我想我能取得他的信任 让他告诉我他所知道的
I think I can get him to trust me and tell me what he knows.
注意安全
Be safe.
阿拉里克
Alaric.
你好
Hi.
什么情况
Who do we have here?
这是杰里米 杰里米·吉尔伯特
This is Jeremy-- Jeremy Gilbert.
他有点
He is a little...
-未成年吗 -是的
-Underage? -Yeah.
是的 我看出来了
Yeah. I can see that.
我希望你能给他一些
I was hoping you could give him one
快速补给液
of those rapid rehydration
治疗宿醉一类的东西
hangover cure type things.
哦 好的 你是说 我们留给
Oh, yeah. You mean, the ones we reserve
专业运动员和第三世界
for professional athletes and starving children
饥饿的孩子们的那种
in third-world countries.
是的 我想我们先做个完全的检查
Yeah. I think we'll start with a full workup--
物理 血液 病毒
physical, blood, toxicology.
好的 为什么你不顺便加多个
Yeah. Why don't you throw in an STD screening
性病筛查  哈
while you're at it, huh?
-要这样子吗 -是的
-Really? -Yeah.
从走廊下去往右走
Down the hall to the right.
我该问吗
Do I want to know?
这是一个神秘学教授
It's just another day in the life
生活中的某一天
of an occult studies professor.
嗯 如果还包括监护喝醉的傻逼的话
Well, if that entails supervising drunk morons,
那我们的共同点可比我想得多
then you and I have a lot more in common than I thought.
啊
Ah.
我知道 对不起 凯伦
I know, and I'm sorry Karen.
杰伊是个好孩子
Jay was a good kid.
我保证 你会第一时间知道消息的
I promise. You'll be the first one to know.
好的
Ok.
特里普 你还好吗
Tripp, are you ok?
不
No.
不 我刚告诉了杰伊的父母
No. I just told Jay's parents
我是那个发现他们儿子
that I was the one who found their son
昨晚死在森林里的人
dead in the woods last night.
我听说了
I heard.
你知道发生了什么吗
Do you know what happened?
你说呢
You tell me.
他和你一起去聚会
He went to the party with you.
我不知道
I don't know.
他喝醉了 我说过要送他回家
He was drunk. I offered to give him a ride home,
他说他要走路
and he said he'd walk.
我应该开车带他回家
I should have driven him home.
好的
Ok.
我要去警长那录口供
I'm gonna give the sheriff my statement
试试弄清楚杰伊发生了什么
and try to make sense of what happened to Jay.
等等 也许我应该和你一起去
Wait. Maybe I should go with you.
我可能是看到杰伊的最后一个人
I might have been the last person to see Jay alive.
好的 就这样 我们走吧
Ok. Done. Let's take a ride.
我工作时需要有点消遣
I need to be entertained while I work.
地狱的故事 请
Hell story, please
提醒我不要杀死他
Remind me not to kill him.
也许告诉他你的故事
Maybe telling him your story will take
会转移你的注意力
your mind off of it.
你到底在哪一边
Whose side are you on?
在能回到我们爱的人身边的那一边
The side where get to go home to the people we love.
好吧
Fine.
1994年五月 我住在这
In May 1994, I was living here.
我回家来回归正途
I'd come home to walk the straight and narrow.
我能喝一口那个吗
Can I have a sip of that?
我很饿
I'm starving.
当然
Sure.
哟
Whew.
嗯 很不错 对吗
Mmm. It's good, right?
嗯 嗯
Uh-uh.
哦 是吧 我不记得
Oh, yeah. I can't remember
那个松鼠是被车撞死的
if that squirrel was roadkill
还是我用捕鼠器抓住的
or one I caught in the rat trap.
还是更希望它是被撞死的
Better hope it was roadkill, though,
因为捕鼠器上都是老鼠屎
because the rat trap was full of rat droppings.
转转你的舌头
Swish your tongue around.
它感觉像头发 还是
Does it feel like hair, or is it more
更像粒状的小球
of a grainy pellet?
嗯
Ugh.
你好啊 扎克
How's it going Zach?
怎么去杂货店买这么多东西
What's up with all the grocery trips?
哦 家里有个人
Ah. One of the boarders
想吃蓝莓煎饼
is craving blueberry pancakes.
你知道 也许该我来管理
You know, maybe I should run
塞尔瓦多家
the Salvatore boarding house.
你好
Hi.
接过扎克的位置
Take over for Zach,
和盖尔和睦共处
get in good with Gail.
她在服马鞭草
She's on Vervain.
扎克也是
So is Zach,
所以 别对他们动手
which means hands off.
太棒辣 我们的救世主是疯的
Perfect. Our savior's insane
还得了嗜睡症
and narcoleptic.
不 不 不 我清醒着呢
No, no, no. I'm awake.
让我猜猜 你杀了
Let me guess-- you killed
那个孕妇
the pregnant woman.
闭嘴 卡伊 你都没听清楚
Shut up, Kai. You weren't listening.
我睡着也能听到
I was listening in my sleep.
你和你的远侄扎克出去闲逛
You were hanging out with your distant nephew Zach,
那个你叫扎克叔叔的人
who you called uncle Zach
因为那样没那么混乱
because that's not confusing.
加上孕妇盖尔
Plus pregnant lady Gail,
她成为了你的目标
who had a big bull's-eye on her chest.
明白了
Got it.
告诉我你没有杀死一个孕妇
Tell me you didn't kill a pregnant woman.
哦 绝对就是这样
Oh, that's totally what happened.
要不然为什么今天会是他的地狱
Why else would today be his personal hell?
哦 又来了
Oh, here we go.
你之所以现在还活着
The only reason that you're alive right now
是因为我以为你可以带我们离开这儿
is because I thought you could get us out of here
能帮助我们
and you could help us,
但你没有任何办法
but you don't have any answers.
你只是一个满手果酱的幼稚男孩
You're just a man-child with jam on your fingers!
好的 那么
Ok then.
想回家 我们需要用到
To get home, we'll harness the power
一件神秘的古物
of the eclipse
来控制月蚀的能量
using a mystical relic.
它被称作运星
It's called an Ascendant,
它看起来长这样 达蒙
and it looks like this, Damon.
我们最后拥有它的时候
The last time we had it was
是在西北太平洋
in the pacific northwest.
俄勒冈州
Oregon.
我们
We?
它属于我们家族
It belonged to my family.
所以给你一点血让你开始动手
So here's a little blood to get you started.
现在我们只需要一个定位咒语
Now all we need is a locator spell
来找到它的下落
to pinpoint its whereabouts.
你能带我们出去了吗 邦邦
Think you can find our ticket out here, Bon Bon?
见鬼 是的
Hell, yeah.
她很可爱
She's cute.
死之前是
Was cute.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我也是 但都结束了
Me, too, but what's done is done.
因此在纳完税 交完社保
So after taxes and social security
和医保之后 我还剩206.03 美元
and health insurance, I'm left with $206.03
这是我这周的生活费了
to spend for the week.
想去喝点酒吗
You want to get drunk?
斯特凡 你连医保都有
Stefan, health insurance?
嗯 为了能重新开始
Yeah. The point is to start over,
尽可能去过人类的生活
pretend to be as human as possible.
是吗 意思是不再用吸血鬼特权
Oh, ok. So no vampire privileges,
不再有包袱 不再使用任何从前用过的东西了
no baggage, nothing from our old lives whatsoever, huh?
那这是什么
Ahem. What's this?
这你可难倒我了
You got me there.
达蒙不在这儿
See, Damon isn't around
没人叫它老爷车了 所以
to call it a granny mobile, so...
是的 你哥哥确实很喜欢
Yeah. Your brother really did love
给别人起绰号来折磨他们
to torture people with nicknames
完全就是为了折磨别人
and just plain torture people.
可以这么说吧
That's one way to put it.
所以把桥烧掉 找份没有前途的工作
So your system for moving on requires
就是你重新开始的办法喽
both burning bridges and a dead-end job.
还有更好玩的事情
We haven't even gotten to the fun part.
给公共事业捐款吗
Paying utilities?
不是 是决定未来三十年里
No. Deciding who you want to be
你想成为什么样的人
for the next 30 years.
你可能想成为一名宇航员
Do you want to be an astronaut,
想成为奥林匹克运动员
you want to be an Olympic athlete,
还想逃医学课程
you want to skip med school,
结果 你成为了一名医生
boom, you're a doctor.
继续 来挑战我吧
Go ahead. Challenge me.
我会让你知道我是如何实现的
I'll show you how it's done.
好吧 看看你是块什么料
All right. Let's see what you got.
没问题
Ok.
那孩子简直就是个酒鬼 要给他输盐水
Quite a boozer that kid. Put him on a saline drip.
没给他洗胃算是幸运了
He's lucky I didn't pump his stomach.
是的 他这几个月挺不好过的
Yeah. You know, he's had a rough couple of months.
你把他带到这来就为了给他贴些创可贴
Did you bring him in here to put a band-aid on it
再找些借口吗
and make some more excuses?
不 其实我是到这来
No. I actually came here for some advice
寻求专家意见的
from a professional.
是吗 揍他一顿就行了
Well, a kick in the ass might help.
杰里米也是一样的
Jeremy, too.
听着 如果他像他姐姐一样
Look. If he's anything like his sister,
我保证他会没事的
I'm sure he'll be fine.
我还是个学生的时候
It's nothing I don't treat every single night on campus
每个晚上在学校我也会这么做
or didn't do myself when I was a student.
好的
Ok.
那你呢
What about you?
以前也是聚会达人吗
Former party animal?
噢 是的 我以前老是被人从
Oh, yeah, yeah. I used to get kicked out
图书馆赶出来
of the library all the time, you know,
因为马上就关门了
because it was closing.
是吗 专心研究巫术圣经吗
Right. Head in the Wiccan Bible?
好吧 再给你一个专家建议
Ok. One more piece of professional advice.
当一个事业有成 又很性感
When a successful, sexy,
只是略微有点不自信的医生
only moderately insecure doctor
在和你调情的时候
is flirting with you,
最好不要分散你的注意力
give her your undivided attention.
卡罗琳在寝室里很低调
Caroline's laying low at the dorm,
没有看到莎拉的踪影
no sign of Sarah yet,
这意味着她不是藏起来
which means she's either hiding out
就是在准备在晚间独家新闻上
or she's planning her nightly news exclusive
爆我的料
to out me.
如果她真的想爆你出来
Well, if she does out you,
那你就去别的地方重新开始
then you start your life over somewhere else
摆脱所有的 额 超自然破事
free of all the, uh, supernatural drama.
有道理
Right.
你准备好看我实行我的方法了吗
So you ready to see the system in action?
准备好了
Ready.
很好
All right.
把戒指给我
Hand over your ring.
什么
What?
你的戒指
Your ring.
好吧
Ok.
埃琳娜·威廉姆斯
Elena Williams...
天哪 斯特凡·库伯 你在干嘛
Ohh! Stefan Cooper, what are you doing?
我们已经认识了很长时间了
We've known each other for a very long time now,
你一直都是我最好的朋友
and you've always been my best friend.
而我一直都在爱着你
I have always loved you,
我想和你共度余生
and I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
-你愿意 -等等
-Will you -Wait!
你不会是因为我怀孕了
You're not just proposing to me
才向我求婚的吧
because I'm pregnant, are you?
不 不
No. No.
我向你求婚
I-I am proposing to you
是因为你就是我的最爱
because you are my rock, ok?
你一直都在我身边
You have stood by my side
陪着我一起康复 陪我度过了监狱里的时光
through the multiple rehabs, the jail time,
陪我一起养斗牛时留下的伤
the bull fighting injury.
我是说 是你把我从危险边缘拯救出来
I mean, you have brought me back from the edge,
亲爱的 这个孩子
and, sweetheart, this baby
对我们来说是再美好不过的存在了
is the best thing that ever happened to us.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
愿意
Yes!
喔 噢
Ha! Oh!
你太疯狂了
Aw. You're crazy.
看到了吗 新的身份 新的生活
See that? New identities, new lives.
这很简单
It's easy.
非常感谢你们 谢谢
Thank you all so much. Thank you.
嘛哩嘛哩哄
Phesmatos tribum nas ex viras,
嘛哩嘛哩哄哄
sequitas sanguinem.
感觉不对劲
It doesn't feel right.
也许我需要一个大一点的地图
Maybe I need a bigger map.
也许是你技巧生疏了
Maybe you're just out of practice
现在魔法很烂
and you suck at magic now.
别理他 邦妮
Ignore him, Bonnie.
就当他是一个白噪音机
Pretend he's a white noise machine.
我以前就是这么无视我的兄弟姐妹的
That's how I used to tune out my siblings.
我有一大堆的弟弟妹妹
I grew with a ton of little sisters and brothers
他们都在不停地哭
and all of them constantly yammering,
但是 额 教会了我如何集中注意力
but it, uh, taught me how to focus.
悠着点 大哥
Easy there, big brother.
她还和你不熟
She doesn't know you.
至少也灌她一杯再说
At least buy her a drink.
我能叫你利兹吗
Can I call you Liz?
确定吗
Sure?
你女儿真可爱
Your daughter is so adorable.
是啊 卡罗琳挺难伺候的
Yeah. Caroline's high maintenance,
但这是值得的
but she's worth it.
一定要扔了这张照片
I am so getting rid of that photo.
斯特凡 来给我和扎克拍照片
Stefan, come take a picture of Zach and me.
好的
Sure.
谢谢 斯特凡
Thanks, Stefan.
现在该继续吃我爱吃的东西了
And now back to my cravings.
嘿 额 你的手腕怎么了
Hey. Um, what happened to your wrist?
我不知道
I don't know.
所以这些东西如何帮我们观看日食
So how does thing help us watch the eclipse?
你把它放在你和
You put it in between you
那个热辣的无法直视的事物之间
and the thing that's too hot to look at.
啊 真的有用
Ahh! It works!
我丈夫会觉得你很有趣的
My husband would get a kick out of you.
我们应该邀请你们找天过来吃饭
We should invite you over to dinner sometime.
达蒙 你对盖尔做了什么
Damon, what'd you do to Gail?
出了什么事吗
Is everything ok?
看来这回完蛋了
Looks like the jig is up.
嘿 看着我
Hey. Look at me.
回家 忘记你曾经见过我们
Go home. Forget you ever met us.
嘿 你为什么要吸盖尔的血
Hey. How the hell did you feed on Gail?
她在服马鞭草
She's on Vervain.
放在她的咖啡里
In her coffee.
我上周调了包
I swapped it out last week,
扎克也一样
same for Zach.
这些人都是我的朋友
These people are my friends.
扎克是家人 他们相信我
Zach is family. They trust me.
所以他们会相信我们
And they'll trust us both.
我只是在家里吸 不是吗
Look. I'm only feeding inside the house, right?
抓住 开吃 清除记忆
Snatch, eat, erase.
这完全行得通 斯特凡
It's all completely functional, Stefan.
我告诉过你这是个新的开始
I told you it's a new start.
嘛哩嘛哩轰
...Nas ex viras, sequitas sanguinem.
嘛哩嘛哩轰轰
Phesmatos tribum nas ex viras,
嘛哩嘛哩轰轰轰
sequitas sanguinem.
血液正流向弗吉尼亚州
The blood's moving towards Virginia.
那不对啊
That can't be right.
额 咒语起作用了
Uh-uh. The spell's working.
它指出了神秘瀑布镇
It's showing me Mystic Falls.
它感觉很
It feels so...
接近
Close.
它就在
It's right...
这里
Here.
很好
Very good.
那就是运星吗
That's the Ascendant?
唯一的一个
The one and only.
谢谢你的心理游戏 蠢货
Thanks for the mind games, jackass.
这只是另一个小测试
It was just another little test
以确保邦妮的魔法
to make sure Bonnie's magic
能足够的精确
was precise enough for the spell.
我相信你已经准备好了
I do believe you're ready.
收拾好你的行李
Pack your bags.
我们要回家了
We're going home.
神秘瀑布镇  1994年
哦
Ohh.
我没弄明白 达蒙
So here's what I don't get, Damon.
你为什么想方设法地回到我的生活里
Why'd you insinuate yourself back into my life
然后作弊 撒谎 破坏所有的规则
and then cheat and lie and break all the rules?
好吧 我撒谎是因为我知道你会生气
Well, I lied because I knew you'd be mad.
信不信由你 我喜欢呆在这里 斯特凡
Believe it or not, I like being here, Stefan.
啊 啊
Aah! Auugh!
当你决定好好表现的时候
You'll get your daylight ring back
你会拿回你的日光戒指的
when you decide to behave.
现在回答我的问题
Now answer my question.
你为什么回到这来
Why'd you come back here?
因为我想我的弟弟
Because I missed my brother.
我想有一个可以唤起我人性的人 斯特凡
I wanted to have a connection to my humanity, Stefan,
我想再次感受一下
I wanted to feel something again,
当我决定回家的时候
and when I decided to come back home,
这一切都涌上心头
it all came rushing back
就像我希望的那样
just like I hoped it would.
哦 恭喜 现在呢
Oh, congrats. Now what?
来吧 伙计 我们一起上路吧
Come on, man. Let's just hit the road,
你和我
you and me.
额 我会让你开我的车
Huh? I'll let you drive my car,
我会带你脱离素食主义
I'll get you off this vegan diet,
再次教你如何填饱肚子
teach you how to feed again.
那肯定很赞 斯特凡
It'll be great, Stef.
呃
Huh?
你觉得怎样
What do you say?
来吧 相信我
Come on! Trust me.
是啊 我可以想象到和你一起公路旅行
Yeah. I can imagine a road trip with you.
是啊
Yeah.
我可以想象你以吸食那些无辜的人为生
I can imagine you feeding on innocent people
然后留下一堆尸体
and leaving a trail of bodies behind.
我可以想象你让我喝人血
I can imagine you making me drink human blood
当我遭受痛苦时嘲笑我
and laughing at me while I suffer.
你该学会成为乐观主义者 斯特凡
Way to be an optimist, Stefan.
我只看到事实 达蒙
I'm just looking at the facts, Damon.
1912年 你说服我再次喝人血
1912, you convinced me to drink human blood again,
这就是我成了一个开膛手的原因
which is why I became a ripper.
1942年 你几乎再次带我走入岐途
1942, you almost pushed me off the rails again
因为你太特么爱折腾了
because you were so damn needy.
1977年 我让我最好的朋友来帮助你
1977, you left my best friend to die
而你就丢下她让她死去
after I sent her to come help you,
现在我终于感到快乐了
and now I'm finally happy,
我有了新生活，我现在过得很好
I have a new life, I'm doing well,
而你 你就是不能接受那一切
and, uh, you just can't handle that,
你可以吗 达蒙
can you, Damon?
我不是想尝试去搞砸
I'm not trying to screw up
你愚蠢的新生活
your dumb new life.
你不用尝试了 达蒙
You don't have to try, Damon.
只要你活在这世上
All you have to do is exist
无论我做什么或者我去哪里
because no matter what I do or where I go,
你会永远和我在一起
you will be with me forever,
试图破坏我一点一滴搭建起来的生活
trying to destroy every single thing that I built.
我不知道有什么理由让我觉得
I don't know why I thought this time
这一次和以往不同
would be any different.
我想让它变得不同
I wanted it to be different,
但是你一直让我失望
but you just keep failing.
所以公路旅行没戏了 是吗
Guess that's a no on the road trip, huh?
公路旅行没戏了
That's a no on the road trip.
所以听卡罗琳说
So according to Caroline,
莎拉还没找到
Sarah's still M.I.A.,
而现在恩佐也不知去向
and now Enzo's missing.
可能在外面杀着别人的女朋友
Probably out killing someone else's girlfriend.
等等 你怀孕了 记得吗
Uh, uh. Pregnant, remember?
我撒过的最愚蠢的谎
Dumbest lie I've ever told.
我可以收回来吗
Can I just take that one back?
不行 但你必须在三十年内
No, but you'll have to reinvent yourself
给自己找个新身份
in 30 years.
如果不这样的话 人们会开始问
If you don't, people will start asking why
为什么你没有变老
you're not getting any older.
但当我第一次遇见你的时候
But when I first met you,
你说你已经离开神秘瀑布镇
you said you'd been away from Mystic Falls
15年了
for 15 years.
是什么让你提前回来
What made you come back ahead of schedule?
像你说的
You said it yourself.
我遇见了你
I met you.
自1864年以来 我一直是一个木匠
Since 1864, I have been a carpenter,
救护车司机 移徙工人
an ambulance driver, a migrant worker,
高中生
high-school student.
那么为什么这次是一周200块钱
So then why auto mechanic
的汽车修理工
for 200 bucks a week?
没有理由
No reason.
是啊 这一定很辛苦 飘荡不安
Yeah. It must be hard, all that change
没有一个稳定的生活
without a constant in your life.
我们还没谈过你哥哥的问题
We haven't talked about your brother.
听你把达蒙称呼成我的哥哥
A little weird to hear you refer to Damon
有点奇怪
as just my brother.
那我还该怎么称呼他
What else would I call him?
那我也不知道了
I don't even know anymore.
不知道了 那是什么意思
Anymore? What does that mean?
算了 这 额 这不重要
You know what? It's, uh, it's not important.
一切都会改变 不是吗
Things change, right?
致改变
To change.
谁在乎其他人怎么想呢 对吧
Who cares what people think, right?
致改变
To change.
你为什么像个神经病一样来回走
You're wandering around like a crazy man why?
我在找那个正确的位置
I'm looking for the exact right spot.
我们需要找到日食能量聚焦在哪一点
We need to find where the power of the eclipse is focused.
你原本可以一开始告诉我们你有运星
You could've just shown us the Ascendant to begin with.
是啊 但我想感受一下你手放在我胸口的感觉
Yeah, but I wanted to feel your hand on my chest.
他有点问题
There's something not right about him.
你只是不习惯有男人和你调情
You're just not used to guys hitting on you.
你知道 我等不及离开这里
You know, I can't wait to get out of here
和其他人说说话
and talk to somebody else.
在那白痴用那玩意
Can we just have a few lasting seconds of peace
将星星排成一列的时候
while this idiot uses that thing
我们能停战几分钟吗
to get the stars to align?
嘿 探索自然探索得怎样
Hey. What's up with the nature walk?
我用运星找到了
I used the Ascendant to figure out
在日食期间我们应该站立的位置
where we need to be standing during the eclipse.
太好了 让我们施些魔法
Great. Let's do some magic,
离开这个鬼地方
get the hell out of here.
-俄勒冈州 -什么
-Oregon. -What?
我已经把这份报纸读了上千次了
I've read this paper, like, a thousand times.
那里有些关于俄勒冈州的东西
There's something in it about Oregon.
那里说了什么
What about it?
你知道 卡伊说他有很多兄弟姐妹
You know, Kai said he had all those brothers and sisters?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
“一家庭在波特兰惨遭屠杀”
"Family massacred in Portland"?
唯一失踪的就是长子
The only one missing was the oldest boy,
叫做玛拉基的22岁青年
a 22-year-old named Malachai.
谁会给一个孩子起这种名啊
Who names a kid Malachai?
就好像他们希望我变成恶魔
It's like they expected me to be evil.
那些孩子都被杀死了
All these kids were murdered.
没看到吗 不是所有人都死了
Hello? Not everyone died.
我还是挺疼爱其中一个妹妹的
I had a soft spot for one of my sisters.
不然我早就把她的肺也挖出来
Otherwise, I would have cut her lungs out
不仅仅是脾脏了
and not just her spleen.
什么
What?
没有脾脏你也能活下来
You can survive without a spleen.
我怎么觉得你好像不是在
Something tells me you're not speaking
开玩笑
hypothetically.
好吧 这两个 我 额
Well, these two, I, uh, hung
吊死在楼梯栏杆上
off a stairwell railing.
然后我在她腹部开了一枪
Then I put a hunting knife in her abdomen,
而他 被我淹死在游泳池里
and him I drowned in the pool.
他一直在反抗
He kept fighting me.
我当时在想
I was like,
我把你留到最后才杀死 你这个不懂感恩的小东西
"I saved you for last, you ungrateful little"...
总之 就是这样
Anyway, that was that.
你杀了你全家人
You just killed your whole family?
准确点说是 巫师会
Coven to be precise.
哦 你知道的 全家都是巫师
Oh, you know, a family of witches.
你让她来回折腾那么久 结果你就是个巫师
You've been making her jump through hoops, and you're a witch?
差不多是这样 很明显我没有力量
Sort of yeah. No powers obviously.
噢 当然了 双子座巫师会听说了
Oh, and of course, Gemini coven did not
我的所作所为之后不是很高兴
take it too well when they heard what I did in Portland.
所以他们把我流放到这里
That's why they banished me here.
这地方是个监狱
This place is a prison.
他们为了你而设的
They created it for you.
没错 这不是你的地狱 达蒙
Yep! This isn't your hell, Damon.
是我的地狱
It's mine.
你还说这是场公平的打斗
You call this a fair fight?
你都能算是个吸血鬼祖先了
You're basically an Original vampire.
你杀死过一个吸血鬼祖先
You've killed an Original before.
现在你快给我认真
Now get your head in the game,
或许你能释放点力量
and maybe you'll keep it out of the bottle.
高兴了吗
Happy?
我在试着帮你振作起来
I am trying to help you pull yourself
杰里米
together, Jeremy.
你的问题是什么
Now what is your problem?
我的问题是
My problem
所有人都认为我不应该出问题
is that everyone thinks that I shouldn't have one.
我现在有权利过得很糟
I have the right to be messed up right now.
邦妮死了
Bonnie is dead.
她知道我会这样
She knew it was gonna happen,
她还用电话道的别
and she said good-bye over the phone
就为了你能
just so you...
继续说啊 为了我什么
Keep going. So what?
就为了我能复活 对吗
So I could come back to life, right?
你 埃琳娜 斯特凡 泰勒 恩佐
You, Elena, Stefan, Tyler, Enzo.
她救了所有人 除了她自己
She saved everybody but herself.
听着 杰里米 你想想谈谈什么是怨恨吗
Listen, Jeremy. You want to talk about resentment, huh?
是吗
Is that it?
我的妻子离我而去 就因为她宁愿当个吸血鬼
My wife ran away because she would rather be
也不愿做我的妻子
a vampire than be married to me.
结果发现 是达蒙将她变成吸血鬼的
Come to find out, it was Damon who turned her,
然后她死了
and then she died,
然后是珍娜 她也死了
and then Jenna-- she died,
然后我也死了
and then I died,
然后杀了我妻子的那个人也死了
and then the guy who killed my wife died,
而我其实还有点想他
and I actually kind of miss him,
而现在我还不能和一个女孩说话
and now I can't even talk to a girl
因为我一直想要咬断她的脖子
without fantasizing about tearing into her neck?
我想说的是 杰里米 我怨恨了很多年 很多年
I mean, Jeremy, I have resentment for years, years!
我能懂 好吗
I get it, ok,
但是我找到了继续生活的方法
but I find a way to keep going
因为我们都这样
because that's what we do.
我们会找到了继续生活的方法
We find a way to keep going!
好吗
Ok?
哦
Oh.
是的
Right.
如果我们30年之后
So if we were to run into each other
在某个小镇遇见对方
in some random town in 30 years,
我们会假装我们是陌生人吗
do we pretend like we're strangers?
埃琳娜 我在避开神秘瀑布镇 不是避开你
Elena, I'm avoiding Mystic Falls, not you.
我们能够聊天 能够串门
We can talk, we can visit,
如果你还需要一名汽车修理工
and if you ever need a car repair,
我会把零件以成本价卖给你
I will give you the parts at cost.
再见 斯特凡
Bye, Stefan.
再见
Bye.
嘿 先生
Hey, man.
啊
Ahh.
我注意到你没有祝福我的订婚
Noticed you weren't celebrating my engagement.
为什么
How come?
很难为了一个把我弟弟
Hard to be happy for the guy who put
打得送进医院的男人而高兴
my brother in the hospital.
哦 对的 对的 对的 好吧
Oh. Right, right, right. Ok.
嘿 提醒我一下 是哪个家伙
Hey. Remind me. Which guy was it--
断了鼻子的还是骨折的
broken nose or fractured arm?
我有点喝醉了
I was kind of drunk.
我还在等着你恭喜
I'm still waiting for the congrats
我的订婚呢
on my engagement.
我真的为你感到高兴
"I'm really happy for you."
是的
Yeah.
呵 呵 你就这本事吗
Heh heh. That all you got?
来吧 小子 打我啊 来啊
Come on, man. Hit me. Come on.
哦
Ohh.
你就喜欢这样吗
You frigging enjoying this?
你这变态
You sick freak!
回家 清理
Go home, clean up,
忘了这曾发生的一切
and forget this ever happened.
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
我们不能让凯伊离开这里 好吗
We're not letting Kai out of here, ok?
他刚说了他是一个连环杀手
He just said he's a serial killer.
我不在乎 我想要离开这里
I don't care. I want to get out of here.
你怎么能不在乎 可能是因为
How can you not care? Maybe because of all
你所做的那些可怕的事情
the horrible things you've done?
可能因为杀了一群孩子
Maybe because killing a bunch of kids
对于一个杀了孕妇的人来说
is not a big deal to someone who's murdered
不是什么大问题
a pregnant woman?
我错了吗
Am I wrong?
你没把门关上吗
Did you leave the door open?
没有 为什么
No. Why?
这日食派对好逊
This eclipse party blows.
我穿过院子的时候 我一点都没看到太阳
I didn't see the sun at all when I made it across the yard.
你忘了当我们吸食人血的时候
You forget how much stronger we are
我们有多么强大
when we drink human blood.
扎克
Zach.
达蒙 请别伤害她
Damon, please don't hurt her.
我想要回我的戒指 斯特凡
I want my ring back, Stefan.
好样的
Attaboy.
我永远都摆脱不了你 是吗
I'm never gonna be rid of you, am I?
是的 你摆脱不了了
No. No, you're not
因为在1912年我告诉了你
because in 1912 I showed you
你是谁 斯特凡
who you were, Stefan.
在1942年 我给了你你想要的自由
In 1942, I gave you your freedom,
在1977年 我差点杀了
and in 1977, I almost killed
你最好的朋友 因为你才应该是那个
your best friend because it should have been you
在那儿帮助我的人 斯特凡
there to help me, Stefan.
你欠我的
You owe me,
我要你用永世
and it'll take you an eternity
来偿还
to pay me back.
不
No!
永远痛苦吧 兄弟
An eternity of misery, brother,
就像我承诺过的一样
just like I promised.
哎呦 我可怜的外甥扎克叔叔
Ouch. Poor nephew uncle Zach.
斯特凡强迫扎克叔叔忘记了
Stefan compelled uncle Zach to forget
他的女友和孩子
about the girlfriend and the baby,
但是他无法掩盖掉所有的凶案
but he couldn't cover up all those murders.
创建者协会重新组建了
The founders' council was restarted,
但斯特凡走了 离开了神秘瀑布镇
and Stefan took off, left Mystic Falls
走了大概15年
for about 15 years.
我们都是
We both did,
当我再次看到扎克叔叔的时候
and then when I saw uncle Zach again,
每当我看着他就忍不住想起
I couldn't look at him without remembering
我曾经毁过的一切
that I had ruined everything,
所以当我杀了他 我感到了真正的解脱
so it was a nice relief when I got to kill him.
好吧 现在我们能回去了吗
Ok. Can we go back now?
噢 来吧 邦妮
Oh, come on, Bonnie.
你想回家和你的朋友在一起
You want to go home to your friends,
我想回去让剩下的
I want to go back and give the rest
双子座巫师们痛苦地死去 双赢啊
of the Gemini coven an excruciating death. Win-win.
听我说 我知道这个人不是一个模范公民 邦妮
Look. I know this guy's not a model citizen, ok, Bonnie,
但我得回去
but I got to get back,
不只是为了埃琳娜 也是为了我的弟弟
not just for Elena but for my brother.
对不起 达蒙
I'm sorry, Damon.
道歉对我没有用
Sorry doesn't work for me.
嘿 我们可能有一些分歧
Hey. We might be having a bit of a disagreement,
但不要对她动手
but don't ever lay a hand on her.
现在不是争论这个的时候
Kind of a nonissue now.
错过了今天的日食
Missed today's eclipse.
推迟到明天吧
Rain check for tomorrow.
不
No.
你和警长似乎相处得不太好
So you and the sheriff don't seem to get along.
哦 利兹和我太太高中时是竞争对手
Oh. Liz and my wife were high-school rivals,
争的是谁是
some issue about who was captain
曲棍球队队长
of the field hockey team.
你结婚了吗
You're married?
曾经是
I was.
是的 克里斯在车祸中去世了
Yeah. Kris died in a car accident.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧 这就是我离开神秘瀑布镇的原因
Well, that's why I left Mystic Falls.
太多回忆了
Too many memories.
你和警长说了些杰伊的什么事
So what'd you tell the sheriff about Jay?
哦 就说我看到的
Oh, just what I saw.
呃 大量的血
Uh, tons of blood.
可能是一只美洲狮
Probably a mountain lion.
只是另一起动物的攻击 是吧
Just another animal attack, huh?
你听起来很怀疑
You sound doubtful.
这或许听起来很奇怪
This is gonna sound weird,
但是昨天晚上 杰伊告诉我他正在
but last night, Jay told me that he was
跟踪一只吸血鬼
tracking a vampire.
我的意思是 这很疯狂 对吗
I mean, that's crazy, right?
我要告诉你一些事
I'm gonna show you something.
我以为你同意离开了
I thought you agreed to leave.
我忘了拿外套 斯特凡
I forgot my jacket, Stefan.
那个人怎么回事
What happened with that guy?
我告诉过你我自有一套方法
I told you I have a system.
让某个人揍你一顿这样你才有感觉吗
Letting somebody kick your ass so that you can feel?
你是最没资格说教我的处理机制
You are the last person who should be lecturing
的那个人
me on coping mechanisms.
不是只有你一个人悲伤 斯特凡
You're not alone in your grief, Stefan.
你失去达蒙的时候 我失去了邦妮
I lost Bonnie when you lost Damon,
但是我熬过来了
but I fought through it.
是吗 靠你一个人吗
Yeah? All by yourself?
是的
Yes.
那是很艰难
And it was hard.
我知道你拒我于千里之外
I know that you're pushing me away
因为我从来不喜欢达蒙
because I never liked Damon--
相信我 不是这样的
Believe me, that's not what it is.
我知道他是你的兄弟 我明白
And I know that he's your brother. I get it,
但你为什么要为了这么讨厌的一个人
but why inflict so much pain on yourself
让自己忍受那么多痛苦
for such a hateful person?
我的意思是 他不值得你悲伤
I mean, he doesn't deserve your grief.
你还有其他方法可以重新生活
There's got to be another way that you can move on.
对不起 我只是不能像你一样
I'm sorry that I can't just forget him
忘了他 埃琳娜
like you, Elena.
没有人忘了他
No one's forgetting him.
你忘了
You are.
你抹去了关于他的记忆
You erased him.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你让阿拉里克催眠你去忘记
You had Alaric compel you to forget
达蒙做过的所有的美好的事
every good thing that Damon ever did.
你让他变成了你心目中的禽兽
You made him a monster in your own mind
因为你无法承受
because you couldn't handle the grief
失去他的悲伤
of losing him.
我不相信你所说的一切
I don't believe anything that you're saying.
为什么我要那么做
Why would I do that?
因为你深爱着他
Because you were in love with him,
并且他也深爱着你
and he was in love with you,
当达蒙死了的时候 一部分的你也死了
and when Damon died, a part of you died, too.
哇 哦 天哪 什么 不 不
Wow. Oh, God. What? No, no.
斯特凡 我怎么可能爱上达蒙
Stefan, how could I possibly love Damon?
相信我 很长一段时间以来
Believe me, I asked myself that
我也在问自己这个问题
for a very long time,
最终 我懂了
and then eventually, I saw it.
达蒙唤醒了你
Damon inspired you,
他促使你接受你内心最黑暗的部分
he pushed you to own the darkest parts of yourself,
当你死了的时候 他是唯一一个
and when you died, he was the only one
能让你再次感到活力的人
that could make you feel alive again,
而你让他感觉到人性
and you made him feel human.
你爱达蒙 和我爱他的理由
You love Damon for the same reasons
是一样的
that I love Damon
因为尽管他做过那么多事
because in spite of every single thing
但我们离不开他
that he did we couldn't live without him,
现在你不需要这样
and now you don't have to,
但我还要承受
but I do,
所以我要用我的方式去做
so I'm gonna do it my way.
你就按你的方式做
You can do it yours.
这是哪里
What is this place?
这是一个秘密
A secret.
我只与我信任的人分享秘密
A secret I only share with people I trust.
你记得那个夏天镇上的天然气泄漏吗
You remember the gas leak in town over the summer?
我回来确认我的祖母是否平安
Well, I came back to make sure my grandmother was ok.
那么多年来我第一次回去
First time I've been back in years.
当我穿过镇的边界的时候
When I crossed the town border...
一些东西改变了
something changed.
回忆如潮水般涌来
Memories came flooding back.
我意识到我的妻子
I realized that my wife
不是在车祸中死去
didn't die in a car accident.
她是被谋杀的
She was murdered,
在我面前被吸干了血
drained of her blood right in front of me,
那个杀人者让我相信
and the killer made me believe
我要为她的死负责
I was responsible.
我要找出是什么怪物
I had to find out what kind of monster
能够这么做
could do all that.
吸血鬼
Vampires--
他们真的存在
they are real,
而其中一只吸血鬼杀死了我妻子
and one murdered my wife,
但是这只
but this is the one
杀了杰伊的吸血鬼
who murdered Jay,
我会让他说出他所有
and I'm gonna get him to name all
吸血鬼同伴的名字
his vampire buddies,
从那只咬了你的朋友莎拉的吸血鬼开始
starting with the one who bit your friend Sarah.
莎拉
Sarah?
你要是敢动
You try anything,
我会报警向全世界揭露
and I call 911 and out your vampire sister
你的吸血鬼姐姐
to the world.
嘿 放轻松 你想怎样
Hey. Just take it easy. What do you want?
答案 我昨晚整理房子的时候
Answers. I found this when I was
发现了这张照片
tossing the house last night.
这是我的妈妈
That's my mom,
我能认出来的原因是
and the reason I know this is
因为我从小就有了这张照片
because I've had this since I was a baby.
我妈妈是个无名氏
My mom was a Jane Doe.
当他们把有6个月身孕的她遗弃在医院的时候
Her body was still warm when they dumped it
她的身体依旧温暖
at the hospital 6 months pregnant.
护士认为我也在送达医院前死亡了
The nurses thought I was DOA, too,
但是一位医生做了紧急破腹产
but one doctor did an emergency C-section,
我活了下来
and I survived.
我在育婴箱里生活了3个月
I lived 3 months in an Incubator.
他们不知道谁是我的爸爸
They didn't know who my dad was,
我也不知道
and neither did I,
但是我找到了这张照片
but then I found this.
你的爸爸是扎克·塞尔瓦托
Your dad is Zach Salvatore.
你怎么能就这样毁了我人生中这一整章节的记忆
How could you obliterate an entire chapter of my life?
埃琳娜 虽然我也很想认为
Look, Elena. As much as I like to think
自己充满智慧
that I am full of wisdom,
但我想我们是时候停止
I think it's time we stop pretending
假装我知道什么是最好的了 好吗
that I actually know what's best, ok?
听我说 我现在把我自己的问题理清楚了
Look. I've got my own issues to sort out right now,
我认为这个能够比我自己
and I think this will explain it much better
解释得更清楚
than I can.
亲爱的自己 如果你正在读这话
"Dear me, if you're reading this,
那么有人泄露了这个
"Then somebody spilled the beans
关于你选择性的失忆的秘密
"About your selective memory loss.
我的钱在卡罗琳那
"My money's on Caroline.
是的 你爱达蒙
"Yes, you loved Damon.
你耗尽全部的激情爱着他
"You loved him with a passion that consumed you,
而当达蒙去世的时候
"And then when Damon died,
他留下的伤痕太深 太痛
"The void he filled was too deep, too dark.
和你的灵魂伴侣面对永生
"Facing an eternity with your soul mate,
你贸然行事
"You went off the deep end.
你变成了你不想成为的那种人
"You turned into someone that you weren't,
一个魔鬼
"A monster.
阿拉里克能恢复你失去的记忆
"Alaric can restore your lost memories.
你只需要开口
"All you have to do is ask,
但我希望你别这么做
"But I hope that you don't.
我尝试过别的方式
"I tried it the other way.
我没能使痛苦结束
"I didn't see an end to the pain.
我希望你能重新发现自我
"I want you to rediscover yourself
就算没有那个让你认识自己的人在身边
"In the absence of the one who defined you.
如果你对未来有任何一点希望
"If you feel any hope for the future at all,
那么你已经开始好转
"Then you're already better off.
你得到了一个重新开始的机会
"You've been given a chance to start over.
我希望你好好把握它
"I want you to take it.
我希望你开心
I want you to be happy."
所以你想我怎么做
So what do you want me to do?
你能先收着它吗
Can you hold on to that,
好好放着 以免我需要再读一遍
keep it safe in case I ever need to read it again?
因为羞耻来吃东西了
Shame eating?
在想着那个怀孕的女人
Thinking about that pregnant lady.
她喜欢吃煎饼
She had a thing for pancakes.
你就记得这些吗
That's what you remember?
你记得 不是吗
You remember it, don't you?
你每天都做煎饼
You make pancakes every day.
因为我无聊
Because I'm bored.
不 因为你在惩罚你自己
No. Because you're punishing yourself.
你把这里称为你的地狱
You called this place your hell.
那意味着你感到悔恨
That means you feel remorse.
这是你与卡伊不同的原因
That's what makes you different than Kai.
这意味着你还有希望
It means there's hope for you.
听着 我们还可以离开这里 邦妮
Look. We can still get out of here, Bonnie.
我们可以把运星那个装置偷过来
We can just steal that Ascendant contraption,
搞清楚凯伊知道些什么
find out what Kai knows.
我们抛下他
We'll ditch him.
反正他也没有任何力量
He doesn't have any powers anyway.
事实上没这么简单
Actually, it's not that simple.
你还再别那样做 这很吓人
You got to stop doing that. It's creepy.
是这样的 我有特殊的魔法效应
Here's the thing. I have a peculiar effect on magic.
我不能自己施展魔法
I can't generate it myself,
但是我能暂时从别的东西上吸取一点
but I can consume it from others temporarily.
家人都叫我讨厌鬼
Family called me an abomination.
那太伤我感情了
That hurt my feelings.
啊
Unh!
好吧 我们知道了 呃
Ok. We get it. Ugh.
你知道为什么巫师会和我相处不来了吧
You can see why my coven and I didn't get along.
我闻到了最后通牒的气息
I smell an ultimatum.
如果我消耗了邦妮所有的魔力
If I consume all of Bonnie's magic,
我就会杀了她
I am just gonna end up killing her,
但是如果我们合作
but if we work together,
我们就可以友好地一起回家
we can all go home as friends,
或者我可以吞噬她的魔力
or I can devour her magic,
杀了你们俩再独自回家
kill you both and go home alone.
那会是怎样呢
What's it gonna be?
有人吗
Hello?
艾薇
Ivy.
斯特凡 我感觉很不好
Stefan, I don't feel so good.
你的朋友恩佐让我喝他的血
Your friend Enzo made me drink his blood,
现在我非常饥渴
and now I'm just so thirsty.